(ｴﾚｲﾝ･回想)((あっ))
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((おっ 発見～！ ほっ！➡
Ah, there it is.
A lick will add ten years to your life.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((♬ ひと口飲～めば
１００年 長生き))
A swallow will add a hundred!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
((♬ 全部飲～めば 永遠の命))
Drink it all, and you'll live forever!
あれが 聖女に守られしお宝
｢生命の泉｣｡➡
So this is the Fountain of Youth,
protected by the Guardian Saint.
Drink the water flowing from the cup and
you'll be granted eternal life, or so they say.
その杯から あふれる水は➡
飲んだ者に
永遠の命を与える… か))
((だいぶ
話に尾ひれが付いたもんだな～))
Seems the story was pretty exaggerated, though.
((宝を守る聖女なんて
どこにもいねぇじゃ… あっ))
I don't see a Guardian Saint protecting the treasure.
Ah...
((うん？ 嬢ちゃん
こんな所で迷子かぁ？))
Huh?
Are you lost, little girl?
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)((泉を守ってるの))
((ん？ あっ？))
I'm protecting the fountain.
From bandits like you.
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)
((あなたのような賊からね))
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((なっ!? うおぉ～！➡
Whoa! I'm gonna die!
死ぬ～～…))
バタン！
ガン
(ﾊﾞﾝ)うっ…｡
あぁ… ふあぁ～！
(ﾎｰｸ)おめぇら 起きろ～！
Hey, guys! Wake up!
≪朝飯の時間だぜ！
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)んん… あっ｡
It's time for breakfast!
Morning, Elizabeth!
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)おはよう エリザベス｡
ケガは どうだ？
How're your injuries?
はい もうだいぶ｡
Ah, they're more or less okay.
えっと…
おはようございます｡
Oh, and... good morning.
うん｡
今 ほどきますね｡
I'll untie you now.
おう 優しくな｡
Thanks.
Please be gentle.
This is a tale of humans and beings from other worlds.
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
In olden times, the Holy Knights fought alongside three tribes to seal away the Demon Clan.
＜聖騎士は かつて
他の三つの種族と共に➡
魔神族を闇に葬った＞
＜聖戦と呼ばれた その戦いは➡
It was known as the Holy War, and memory of it has long left the minds of the people.
時を経て 人々の記憶から
消えてなくなった＞
＜ だが 今再び 聖戦が叫ばれる＞
However, a new Holy War has begun.
＜七つの大罪を葬り去れと＞
The battle to banish the Seven Deadly Sins unto oblivion.
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
With unyielding emotions in tow,
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume o tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
Guided by my tenacity,
akiramenu omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume o tsunai da kimi to
Episode 7
The Touching Reunion
あの… ホークちゃん｡
Um, Hawk?
Hmm?
あん？
メリオダス様のこと➡
You don't have to tie up Lord Meliodas so tight next time.
次は 緩めに縛ってくれる？
あれじゃあ ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ様も
よく眠れないわ｡
I don't think he can sleep very well like that.
きつく縛らないと
意味ないだろ！
There's no point unless I do it tight!
Sleeping in the same bed as Elizabeth... His hands would run free!
エリザベスちゃんと
同じベッドで寝るなんて➡
手ぇ出し放題だからな｡
あれくらい当然だぜ！
でも…｡
I have to make sure it's extra tight!
But...
If you think of it like BDSM, it's not half bad.
プレイの一環だと思えば
なかなか快適だぞ｡
BDSM?
プレイ？
次からは エリザベスに➡
Maybe we should tie Elizabeth up next time.
縛ってもらおうかな｡
えっ？
てめぇ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)何？ 何？➡
Why, you...
What are we tying up now?
何縛るの？ ホーク？
違う！
Hawk?
No!
プゴップゴップゴッ！
(一同)ん？
Cap'n, where's the booze?
団ちょ 酒｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)朝から？
It's morning, you know...
バン様 朝食は？
団ちょの まずい飯なんか➡
Lord Ban, what about breakfast?
There's no way in hell I'd eat Cap'n's horrible food.
食えるかっての｡
けっ！
Here.
That's why you cook it yourself.
だったら 自分で作れってんだ｡
センキュ 団ちょ…｡
Thank you, Cap'n—
目指すは 死者の都｡
そこで キングを捜す｡
Our next target is the Capital of the Dead.
We'll look for King there.
Didn't that fat bastard die or something?
クソデブは
死んだって話じゃねぇのか？
That's the only lead we have, so... may as well check it out.
今んとこ
手がかりは それだけだし➡
行ってみようぜ｡
死者の都って➡
What's the Capital of the Dead like, exactly?
どういった場所なのでしょうか？
さあな｡
Beats me.
俺も そういう所があるとしか
聞いたことねぇ｡
I didn't even know the place existed.
死者の都っていうぐらいだから➡
If it's the Capital of the Dead, there'll be ghosts, right?
幽霊が出るんじゃね？
It'll be dim out even in the middle of the day, and there'll be graves lined up everywhere!
昼でも薄暗くて
お墓が ずらっと並んでてよぉ…｡
えっ…｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)虫は いないよね？
There won't be bugs, will there?
はっ！ もし そこに
キングがいたとして➡
If King really is there, would he even be alive?
ほんとに
そいつは生きてるのか？
ホークちゃん やめて！
幽霊ねぇ｡
Hawk, stop it!
Ghosts, huh?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((あっぶねぇ～！➡
That was close.
So that's the Guardian Saint of the fountain.
あれが 泉を守る聖女か｡ へへっ))
((もう大丈夫｡
賊は やっつけたわ))
It's okay now.
I've gotten rid of the bandit.
((≫(ﾊﾞﾝ)♬ ひと口なめれば
１０年 長生き))
A lick will add ten years to your life.
A swallow will add a hundred!
Drink it all, and you'll live forever!
((とう！➡
うわぁ～～…))
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((いってぇ…｡ へへっ！➡
A lick will add ten years—
((はぁ はぁ はぁ はぁ！ うっ！))
((んんっ！ ふん… おわぁ！))
((はぁ はぁ はぁ！))
((くっ！))
Give it a rest!
((いいかげんにしろ！))
((それは こっちが言いたいわ！➡
That's what I'd like to say!
How are you even alive?
だいたい なんで生きてるの!?
人間が この高さから落ちて➡
No human should be able to survive after falling from this height!
無事のはずがないのに！))
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((いや～➡
Well, I happened to land on some branches
うっかり 枝に引っ掛かったり➡
たまたま
木が密集してる所に落ちたり))
or had my fall broken by a large cluster of trees.
((まさか…｡ この森が➡
No way.
Why would the forest save a human?
人間を助けるはず…))
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((かっかっかっかっ！➡
知るかってぇ～の｡
にしても まさか 嬢ちゃんが➡
How should I know?
But I'm surprised that you, little miss, are the guardian of the treasure.
秘宝を守る番人だったとはなぁ))
Guess I'll be serious this time.
((こっちも
マジでやらせてもらうぜ))
Kill and steal...
((殺して奪う…
人間は皆 考えることが同じね))
All humans think alike.
Magic?
(心の声)≪魔力！≫
It's... not alcoholic.
((酒… じゃねぇのな))
((あっ｡ はっ！))
(ﾊﾞﾝ)((じゃ 早速))
Well, down the hatch!
N-No!
((ダ… ダメ～‼))
((俺の人生に かんぱ… いっ!?➡
Cheers to my new life—
なんじゃこりゃ～!?))
((ふぅ…))
What the hell is this?!
Hey, let me go!
((おい 放せってんだ！))
((あなたたち人間に
分かれとは言わないわ))
I don't expect you humans to understand.
But without the Fountain of Youth, all the trees in this forest will die!
((でも ｢生命の泉｣がなくなれば➡
この森は
全て枯れ果ててしまうの))
((諦めて
ここから立ち去りなさい))
Give it up and leave this place immediately.
((うん 分かった))
((えっ…))
Okay, I get it.
You get it?
((分かったって…
よくも そんなうそを！))
How dare you spout such a lie?
((いや～ マジで｡ はははっ！))
Nah, I'm being serious.
Apparently he doesn't know
that I can read people's minds.
≪私が 人の心を
読めることも知らないで≫
(ﾊﾞﾝ)≪しゃあねぇ≫
Guess I've gotta give it up.
The ale made from this forest's wildberries is really good...
≪ここの森の
ワイルドベリーで作ったエールが➡
半端なく うまいんだよなぁ｡➡
さすがに あれが飲めなくなんのは
困るわ｡ はぁ～あ…≫
It'd be a shame if I couldn't drink it anymore.
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)≪この人…≫
≪無駄足かよ≫
This person...
What a wasted trip...
You...
((あなた 一体 何者？))
Who on earth are you?
Can't you tell by looking?
((見りゃ分かんだろ 賊だよ))
I'm a bandit.
((賊のバンで通ってる｡➡
I go by Bandit Ban.
嬢ちゃんは？))
((子供じゃないわ｡➡
You, little girl?
I'm not a child.
I'm Elaine.
エレインよ))
(ﾎｰｸﾏﾏ)ブゴォ～ッ！
おっと｡
We've arrived!
到着～！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)へえ～➡
ここが死者の都？
So this is the Capital of the Dead?
こんな寂れた集落の
ど～こが都なんだ？
How exactly is this desolate
village the Capital of the Dead?
ここが いちばん
死者の都に近いって噂なんだよ｡
From what I've heard,
this village is just the closest to it.
まずは キングと死者の都に関する
情報集めだ｡
First, let's gather some information
on King and the Capital of the Dead.
それと
当面の飯代を稼がねぇとな｡
We have to make some money for food, too.
早速 開店準備だ！
Let's get ready to open up shop!
So it really is true that Cap'n is waitin' tables.
マジで団ちょが
店ちょ やってるよ～｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)働く団長も す･て･き！
Captain is so dreamy when he's working!
お前らも働くんだ｡
You guys are working as well!
呼び込みは任せたぞ 大看板娘！
僕!?
You're in charge of attracting customers, big eye-candy!
Me?!
And I'll be counting on the
Jailbreak Chef for tasty food!
うまい飯を頼んだぞ 脱獄料理人！
俺が？
Who, me?
Are you sure you didn't mean "crap" food?
臭い飯の間違いじゃなくて？
うまい！ と言いたいが
マジな話 これが うまいんだな｡
No, his food is seriously delicious.
It'll make you wanna shout out, "Tasty!"
まあ 待て待て…｡
さあ 仕事だ｡
Hey, wait a sec...
It's time for work!
じゃんじゃん働こう｡
私にも お仕事させてください｡
Get to it, guys!
Please let me work as well.
もう
ケガは なんともありませんし｡
My injuries aren't severe anymore.
無理だけはすんなよ？
Don't force yourself.
はい！
おっ｡
Yes!
団長～！ 看板娘だなんて➡
Captain!
Making me a showgirl...
僕 僕… すっごいうれしい！
I-I'm so happy!
ありがとう 団長～｡
僕 いっぱい頑張るねぇ！
Thanks, Captain!
I'll make sure I work extra hard, okay!
おう 期待してるぞ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)うん！
All right, I'll keep my hopes up!
Yes!
そうだ バン｡
食糧庫は店の裏にあ… あれ？
Oh right, Ban!
The pantry is at the back of the shop—
Huh?
He—
あいつ～！
逃げたな｡
Ran off.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)団ちょも 冗談きついぜ｡➡
Cap'n must be joking.
I mean, how much information could you
even get from a run-down village like this?
だいたい こんな シケた村で
なんの情報が集まるってんだ～？
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)おいしいお酒～！
The best drinks in town!
Boar Roast, a bar where cute waitresses serve you!
かわいい看板娘が お出迎えの➡
豚の丸焼き亭だよ～！
｢豚の帽子｣亭な｡
It's Boar Hat.
There'll be lots of special service!
い～っぱいサービスしちゃうぞ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)しかしまあ➡
But, man...
This place is seriously dilapidated.
見事な荒れ具合だな｡ あっ｡
Elle...
(ﾊﾞﾝ)エレ…｡
(ｴﾚﾝ)えっ？
Hmm?
あっ…｡ いや 悪ぃ｡
No, never mind...
There's no way...
んなわけねぇかぁ｡
≪バタッ(倒れる音)
メリオダス様｡
ん？
Lord Meliodas?
Hmm?
Lord King... What type of person is he?
キング様って
どんな方なんですか？
Hmm, let's see...
う～ん そうだなぁ｡
ひと言で言うと 七つの大罪の➡
In a nutshell, he's like the
mascot of the Seven Deadly Sins.
マスコット… ペット的な位置？
Or like a pet, I guess?
Hey now, that pet thing has to be a joke.
おいおい ペットは 勘弁しろって｡
飲食店で
畜生を飼うって どうなわけ？
What kind of restaurant keeps a pet inside?
Funny hearing that from you.
お前が それを言う？
あっ キングといえば 昔➡
Well, about King.
バンのヤツが ぬいぐるみ集めに
はまったときさ…｡
A long time ago, Ban went through
a phase of collecting stuffed animals.
ぬいぐるみ？
かわいいな それ｡
Stuffed animals?
That's kinda cute!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
((うぼぉ～！ おいら 悲しいよ))
I'm so sad!
((うっぜ～))
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)((王国中のぬいぐるみを➡
Give it a rest, will ya.
Stealing all the stuffed animals in the kingdom...
さらうなんて…｡
この子たち一人一人には➡
Every one of these guys has memories and
feelings of their owner stuffed inside them!
持ち主の子との
たくさんの思い出や➡
大切な気持ちが詰まってるんだ！
君ってヤツは…➡
But you...
君ってヤツは ひどいよ～！))
((いや～➡
You're just so horrible!
No, they're stuffed with cotton or old clothes, aren't they?
詰まってんのは 綿か ボロ布…))
((やめて～！))
No, stop it!
＜キングは
夜通し泣きじゃくり続け➡
King cried through the night.
朝方 バンが ご満悦で
いびきを かきはじめたころ…＞
Around the time of morning Ban was finally satisfied and started snoring...
((ぐわぁ～！ ぐぅ…))
(子供)((ママ！
僕のクマさんが帰って来たよ))
Mama, Mr. Bear came back!
(子供)((おかえり マルチェロ！))
(子供)((破けた所が直ってる))
Welcome back, Marcello!
And your tear was fixed, too!
(子供)((きっと 妖精さんが
取り返してくれたんだよ！))
I bet a fairy came by and returned it to me!
少し変わってるみたいですけど➡
That's a little different than what I had imagined.
とても 心の優しい方なんですね
キング様って｡
But Lord King seems like he's a really kind person.
それに引き換え バンは
本当に ろくでなしだな｡
On the other hand, Ban is really a good-for-nothing.
相当 仲悪かっただろ？
それがどうして｡
I bet the two of them got along real well.
Why do you think that?
King was always right behind Ban, wherever he went.
キングは しょっちゅう
バンの後ろをついて回ってた｡
Maybe it was to clean up Ban's mess.
バンの
尻拭いのためかもしんねぇけど｡
まっ なんだかんだ➡
Either way, they were an unlikely dynamic duo.
いいコンビだったんじゃねぇの？
ふふふっ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)お客 来ないよ～｡
一人も来ないよ…｡
Customers aren't coming...
Not even a single person...
Hey...
(ﾊﾞﾝ)お～い｡ おい 嬢ちゃん｡
んん…｡
Hey, little girl!
気が付いたか？
あっ｡
You awake?
Get your hands off Ellen!
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)エレンから手を放せ！
あ～ん？
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)い… 妹を どうする気だ!?
What are you doing to my sister?!
Hey, you, if you're her brother,
(ﾊﾞﾝ)おい てめぇ 兄貴なら➡
are you giving her enough food to eat?
妹に 飯
ちゃんと食わせてんのか～？
Shut up! Get away from my sister!
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)
黙れ！ 妹から離れろ！
I'm asking you if you give her enough food to eat.
飯を食わせてんのか
聞いてんだよ 俺は｡➡
I'm taking her.
連れてくぞ？
うっ うぅ…｡➡
うわぁ～！
ドスッ！
Brother, this person looked after me!
お兄ちゃん！
この人は 私を介抱してくれたの！
えっ？ ぼ… 僕…｡
Eh?
I...
ごめんなさい！
僕は どう 罪滅ぼしをしたら…｡
Sorry!
I...
How can I atone for my sin?
罪滅ぼし？
ガキが 何言ってんだよ｡
Atone for your sin?
Whatcha talking about, kid?
だって！ あっ…➡
You know, I...
Your wound?
傷が…｡
一つ教えてやる｡➡
Let me tell you something.
本当の罪ってのは➡
A real sin...
滅ぼすことなんてできねぇのさ｡
is something you can never atone for.
ドスッ‼
あっ｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)よく分かってるじゃない｡
Seems you understand that well.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ぐはっ！
(２人)あぁ…｡
やあ バン｡
Yo, Ban.
ねえ
久々の感動の再会じゃないか｡➡
Hey, it's our touching reunion that's long overdue.
君は
おいらに 何かひと言ないの？
Don't you have anything to say to me?
誰？ お前｡
Who... are you?
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)おいらが誰か… だって？➡
Who am I, you ask?
そんなことも忘れたのかい？
You've forgotten that as well?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)みじんも思い出せねぇわ｡
悪ぃな～｡
I haven't the slightest idea.
Sorry 'bout that.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
ふっ｡ 確かに どうでもいいね｡➡
Well, it doesn't matter.
The important thing is that...
重要なのは 君が…｡
がっ！
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)強欲の罪
強欲の罪のバンだということさ｡➡
you're Ban, the Fox's Sin of Greed.
それとも
こう言った方がいいのかな？
Or should I say...
Ban, the Undead.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)不死身のバン｡
I don't like your attitude, pal.
気に入らねぇな～ その口ぶり｡
俺の何を知ってる？
What do you know about me?
はぁ… 君の罪さ｡
Your sin.
Huh?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ああ？
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)おいらのことは➡
Even if you don't remember who I am, you remember your own sin, right?
思い出せなくても
自分の罪は覚えているだろ？➡
君の犯した 深い… 深い罪｡➡
The grave, grave sin that you committed...
To satisfy your own greed.
自分の強欲を満たし
永遠の命を手に入れるために➡
As the price for immortality.
You killed the Guardian Saint of the Fountain of Youth.
｢生命の泉｣の聖女を殺した｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)おい ガキども～ 邪魔｡
Hey, brats,
you'll get in the way.
Let's go, Ellen!
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)行こう エレン！
(ｴﾚﾝ)でも…｡
But...
Hit the mark, did I?
図星なんだね｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)だから お前は 誰だっつぅの！
ドゴン！
I asked you who the hell you are!
Either way, I'm glad you came.
それにしても よく来てくれたね➡
まんまと
おいらの罠にはまってさ｡
Baited by my trap and all.
逃がさないよ｡
You're not getting away.
飛び回る蜂… 飛び回る蜂！
The Flying Bee, Bumblebee!
Bumblebee
Flying Bee
意味が分かんねぇなぁ！
I don't get what you're trying to do at all!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)彼女に見せてあげたいんだ｡
自分を殺した罪深い男が➡
I want to show it to her.
The sight of her sinful murderer...
惨めに這いつくばり
苦悶する姿を｡
cowering and writhing in anguish.
Like I said...
だからよぉ… へっ！
はっ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)てめぇは 一体…｡
Just who the hell—
こらっ！
カポン
Hey!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)おい 団ちょ 邪魔すんなよ｡
C'mon, Cap'n.
Stay outta my way!
お前こそ
仕事サボって 何やってんの？
What are you doing, skipping out on work?
What am I doing?
何って
あの誰だか分からねぇチビに➡
This random midget picked a fight with me !
ケンカ 吹っかけられたんだよ｡
ん？
一張羅が台なしだ｡
My clothes are ruined now.
Hey, what's all the ruckus about?
お～い
さっきから 何騒いでんの？ ん？➡
Oh!
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)キング！
King!
ん!? あれのどこがキングなんだ！
How the hell is that King?!
Well...
まあ… 若干 痩せたか？
He lost a bit of weight?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)若干じゃねぇし
それ以前の問題だ！
More than a bit, but that's not the issue here!
King! We've been looking for you!
キング！
僕たち キングを捜してたんだ｡
また会えて うれしいよ！
I'm happy to see you again!
Here ya go. Eat up!
ほらよ 食え｡
(ｴﾚﾝ ﾙｲｼﾞ)うわぁ～！
おいしそうな香り｡
Wow, it looks delicious!
プゴッ プゴッ…｡
なっ？
Right?
But... we don't have any money—
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)でも 僕たち お金なんて…｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)食わねぇなら➡
If you're not gonna eat, I'll feed it all to the pig.
全部 豚の餌にすんぞ～？
プギッ!?
Let's dig in then!
(ｴﾚﾝ ﾙｲｼﾞ)いただきます！
プギ～ッ！
(ｴﾚﾝ)おいしい｡
おっ 俺にも おこぼれを…｡
Delicious!
Please leave some leftovers for me...
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)
おにいちゃん 本当に ありがとう｡
Thanks so much, mister!
Give and take.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ギブ･アンド･テ～イク｡
代わりに➡
In return, tell me where the
Capital of the Dead or whatever is.
死者の都とやらの場所を教えろ｡
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)えっ？
おい バン｡
キングは見つかったんだ｡
Hey, Ban, we've already found King.
行く必要は もうなくなったろ？
We don't have to go there anymore, right?
あれが キングなわけねぇだろ｡
There's no way that was King.
本物だって｡
偽物だ｡
He was real.
It was a fake.
本物｡
偽物！
He was real!
Fake!
You guys want to go to the Capital of the Dead too?
あんたたちも
死者の都に行きたいの？
(２人)｢も｣？
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)さっきの子も➡
"Too?"
That kid asked a few times as well.
何度か聞いてきたんだ➡
He said he needed to go to the
Capital of the Dead, no matter what.
死者の都に
どうしても行きたいんだって｡
King did?
キングも？
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)うん ずっと探してるみたい｡
Yeah.
Seems like he's been searching forever.
そんなへんぴな
所にあるのか？
Is it in some really remote place?
ううん すぐそばだよ｡
No, it's right around here.
What do you mean?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)どういうこと～？
The entrance to the Capital
of the Dead is in this village.
(ﾙｲｼﾞ)死者の都への入り口は
この集落にあるんだ｡➡
But you can't just go there because you want to.
でも 行こうと思って
行ける場所じゃない｡
(２人)ん？
謎掛けにゃ興味ねぇな｡
I'm not interested in riddles.
I see.
なるほど｡ つまりは➡
In other words...
こういうことか！
プゴッ！
it's like this!
違うと思います｡
I don't think that's it...
Is it like a grave that's usually hidden or something?
ふだんは隠されている
墓とか… か？
お墓じゃないよ｡ 死者の都は➡
It's not a grave.
The Capital of the Dead is where those who have died go on living.
死んだ人たちが住む国なんだって｡
あの世ってことか？
そんな所 どうやって…｡
So it's like the afterlife?
How can we go to a place like that?
どうやれば
こいつに届くんだ？
How can I reach it?!
Have you been there?
お前は行ったことあんのか～？
あるわけないよ｡ そんなの
迷信に決まってるじゃない｡
No way! It's just superstition!
(ｴﾚﾝ)｢何にも代え難い
死者との思い出が➡
"A priceless memory shared with the
deceased will open the path to the Capital..."
都へといざなう｣｡
隣のおじいちゃんが
よく言ってました｡➡
The old man next door always used to say that.
ごめんなさい それくらいしか…｡
I'm sorry.
That's all we know.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)飯代には
十分な情報だ｡
That's more than enough to cover your food.
Thanks, Elaine.
ありがとよ エレイン｡
あ… あの～ 私 エレン｡
Um, I'm Ellen...
おっと 悪ぃな エレン｡
Ah, right... Sorry, Ellen.
Come on, there's still food left.
おらっ まだ残ってんぞ｡
(ｴﾚﾝ)うん！
キング様はどうして 死者の都に➡
I wonder why King wants to
go to the Capital of the Dead.
行きたがっているのでしょうか？
さてさてさ～て➡
Well, let's see...
I guess we'll know once we get there!
俺たちも行ってみりゃ分かるだろ｡
King, why did you run away earlier?
キング さっきは
どうして逃げちゃったのかな？
I'm stupid!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)おいらのバカ！
バカ バカ バカ！ バカ～！➡
So stupid! I'm such an idiot!
あれじゃあ
まるで ディアンヌを見て➡
I made it look like I ran away because I saw Diane!
逃げたと
思われちゃうじゃないか｡➡
うぅ…
でも しかたないじゃないか｡➡
I couldn't help it, though.
久々に会って あんなこと
言われたら… 言われたら！
Especially after hearing her just
come out and say something like that.
What she said...
((また会えて うれしいよ！))
I'm so happy to see you again!
にへ～！➡
ディアンヌってば
相変わらず かわいいな～｡➡
Diane is just as cute as ever!
はっ！ さっきので おいらが
ディアンヌを好きだって➡
But what should I do if that
makes her realize that I like her?
バレたら どうしよう？
どうしよう!?
What should I do?!
それにしても 団長は
１０年前と変わらないというか➡
Nevertheless, Captain hasn't
changed a bit in the last ten years.
How is that even possible?
変化なさ過ぎだろ｡➡
でも 二人とも 元気そうだった｡➡
But... the two of them seem to be doing pretty well.
くっ！ 二人とも➡
You two... Don't be fooled by that scoundrel.
あんな悪党に
だまされちゃダメだ｡➡
バン…
おいらは 絶対 許さないぞ｡
Ban!
I'll never forgive you!
仮に
死者の都があるとしても… だ➡
Even if the Capital of the Dead exists,
あの世じゃ 行きようねぇだろ｡
there's no way to go to the afterlife.
Since it's the afterlife, what if we just kill ourselves?
あの世だけに
死ねば行けるんじゃねぇの？
バカか お前！
Are you stupid?
A priceless memory of the deceased...
死者との思い出が導く… か｡
私 物心 付く前に
亡くなってしまった母に➡
I want to meet my mother who passed away
when I was young, because I never got to know her.
会ってみたいです｡
じゃ ダメだろ｡
That wouldn't work, then.
そ… そうですよね｡
思い出ないですものね｡
Yeah... You're right.
Because I have no memories of her...
(ｴﾚｲﾝ)((バン))
Ban.
((あなたは 何が目的で
｢生命の泉｣を求めるの？))
What's your motive for going after the Fountain of Youth?
Well, let's see...
((そうだな～ ろくでもねぇ人生も
長く生きられりゃ➡
Even though my life hasn't been all that great,
いつかは
いいこと あるかもなぁって➡
I figure that if I live long enough, something good might happen.
そんだけ))
((もし 永遠の命を手にしても➡
But what if you obtain immortality and nothing good happens to you?
いいことなんて何もなかったら？))
((あん？))
Huh?
≫(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)あははっ！
ん？
Ban, that doesn't suit you!
バン 似合わな～い｡
あん？
(ﾊﾞﾝ)なんだこりゃ？
エリザベス お花 かわいいよ｡
What the hell is this?
Elizabeth, the flowers are so pretty!
Wow! What are these flowers?
わあ～！ この花は なんでしょう？
Who cares, they're just flowers!
どうでもいいだろ 花なんて｡
食ったところで
腹の足しになるわけでも… ﾌｶﾞｯ！
Even if we were to eat them, we'd never get full...
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)きれ～い！
≫(ﾙｲｼﾞ)みんな！➡
So pretty!
Guys!
Watch out!
気をつけて！
えっ？ きゃあ！
(ｴﾚﾝ)
おにいちゃん！ おねえちゃ～ん！
Mister! Lady!
(ﾙｲｼﾞ ｴﾚﾝ)あっ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長…｡
ああ｡
Captain...
Yeah...
間違いない 死者の都だ｡
No doubt about it.
It's the Capital of the Dead.
あの中の誰かの思いが
ここへの道を？
One of them had a memory that opened up the path?
Is it possible that my longing to see my mother...
ひょっとして
私の 母に会いたいという思いが？
No... It might be my memories of
the leftovers I was never able to eat.
いや 俺が食いそびれた
残飯たちへの強い思いかもな｡
I have no idea!
心当たり なし！
僕も～｡
Me neither!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)あっ バン！
待て！
Ban!
Wait!
キング!?
King?!
That's him?
あの方が？
なんだ？ なんだ？
What's going on?
団長 どうしよう？
ひとまず 追っかけるか｡
Captain, what should we do?
We'll chase after them for now.
I won't let you get away!
逃がさないよ！
逃がさねぇぞ！
You won't get away from me!
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
ittari kitari de ikidomari yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and defy them all to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang HAJI ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
Let's go, now we can fly high
iku ze Now we can fly high
エレン 見たか？
うん…｡➡
Ellen... Did you see?
Yeah.
あの人たち 行っちゃった｡
Those people... disappeared.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)なるほど｡
死者の都は 実在したようですね｡
I see. I guess the Capital of the Dead does exist.
(ｴﾚﾝ ﾙｲｼﾞ)あっ！
Next Episode's Report
Um, I have a feeling that someone's been following us for a while.
あの… なんか 変な子が 後ろから
ついてきてる気がするんですけど｡
さては 今 はやりの
ストーカーってやつだな｡
Guess it's one of those crazy
stalkers you hear about these days.
Don't make eye contact.
振り返っちゃダメだ｡
でも 全然 足音もしないんです｡
But I can't even hear the sound of his footsteps.
ヤツらは
気配を消すために必死だからな｡
Because they try desperately to stay hidden.
き… 気のせいか ちゅ… 宙に
浮いてる気もするんですけど｡
I-It might be my imagination,
b-but it feels like he's floating in the air...
人間 死ぬ気になれば
なんでもできるもんだな｡
When a person's life is on the line, they can do anything.
Next time, on The Seven Deadly Sins: "The Deadly Pursuer."
次回 『七つの大罪』
｢恐るべき追跡者｣｡
Um, the punchline of the joke isn't
that the person's already dead, right?
っていうか もう死んでる人…➡
とかいう オチじゃないですよね？
Episode 8
The Dreadful Pursuer
Ｇ２０サミット出席のため､
オーストラリアを訪れている安倍
総理大臣は
つい先ほど､同行している記者団と
懇談し､